

ABOUT

After completing my PhD in Robotics and Computer Science, I introduced my love of music and sound into my practice. I'm attracted by the technical aspect of sound and music, since see all of these inextricably linked and also love the creative side of technology and programming. In the last few years, I have specialized myself in development and worked as a full-stack engineer.

CONTACT

- Granada (Spain)
- ☑ d.r.valeiras@gmail.com
- in LinkedIn profile
- github.com/valeiras

David Reverter Valeiras

Doctor of Engineering - Front End Developer

EDUCATION

PhD in Computer Science

Université Pierre et Marie Curie (Paris)

Master Degree in advanced Systems and Robotics Université Pierre et Marie Curie (Paris)

Industrial Engineering, Specialty: Mechanics
E.T.S.E.I. de Vigo (Vigo)

Live Sound Technician

Centro de formación escénica de Andalucía

SKILLS

Programming languages:

TS	Typescript		JS	JavaScript	
티	HTML		티	CSS	
©	C++		ş	Python	
Tools:					
(js)	Node.js		₩	React	
N	Next.js		•	Git	
∞	Arduino		◆	Matlab	
Languages:					
Spanish		Native	English Fluent		

EXPERIENCE

Native French

Fluent

2023-2024: Full-stack developer

Ennubo (Madrid)

2022-2023: Developer of Mekanika

Cabeza Patata (London)

2020-2022: Live Sound Technician

Freelance

Galician

2017-2020: Professional musician

Freelance

2013-2017: Doctorate

Institut de la Vision (Paris)